{
	"name": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice",
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": "When being tailgated by another vehicle while responding to an emergency call, you should:\n\nA. stop the ambulance and confront the driver.\nB. slow down and allow the driver to pass you.\nC. increase your speed to create more distance.\nD. slam on the brakes to frighten the tailgater.\nSee Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques",
			"back": "slow down and allow the driver to pass you."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": "The process of removing dirt, dust, blood, or other visible contaminants from a surface or equipment is called:\n\nA. disinfection.\nB. sterilization.\nC. high-level disinfection.\nD. cleaning.\nSee Phases of an Ambulance Call",
			"back": "cleaning."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": "Regardless of where portable and mounted oxygen cylinders are stored in the ambulance, they must:\n\nA. hold a minimum capacity of 1,500 L of oxygen.\nB. undergo hydrostatic testing on a weekly basis.\nC. be capable of delivering oxygen at 1 to 15 L/min.\nD. be easily identifiable by their bright green color.\nSee Phases of an Ambulance Call",
			"back": "be capable of delivering oxygen at 1 to 15 L/min."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": "Phases of an ambulance call include all of the following activities, except:\n\nA. transferring the patient to the ambulance.\nB. emergency care provided at the scene.\nC. checking equipment on the ambulance.\nD. transport of the patient to the hospital.\nSee Phases of an Ambulance Call",
			"back": "emergency care provided at the scene."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": "Delivering a patient to the hospital involves all of the following activities, except:\n\nA. completing a detailed written report.\nB. restocking any disposable items you used.\nC. giving a verbal report to the triage clerk.\nD. informing the dispatcher of your arrival.\nSee Phases of an Ambulance Call",
			"back": "giving a verbal report to the triage clerk."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": "When driving an ambulance on a multilane highway in emergency mode, you should:\n\nA. remain in the extreme right-hand lane.\nB. pass other drivers on the right side.\nC. remain in the extreme left-hand lane.\nD. drive in the center lane of the highway.\nSee Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques",
			"back": "remain in the extreme left-hand lane."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": "The most common and usually the most serious ambulance crashes occur at:\n\nA. stop signs.\nB. stop lights.\nC. intersections.\nD. railroad crossings.\nSee Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques",
			"back": "intersections."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": "A type _____ ambulance features a conventional, truck cab-chassis with a modular ambulance body that can be transferred to a newer chassis as needed.\n\nA. I\nB. II\nC. IV\nD. III\nSee Emergency Vehicle Design",
			"back": "I"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": "Minimum staffing in the patient compartment of a basic life support (BLS) ambulance includes:\n\nA. an EMT and an AEMT.\nB. at least one EMT.\nC. an EMT and a paramedic.\nD. at least two EMTs.\nSee Phases of an Ambulance Call",
			"back": "at least one EMT."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": "Other than personal safety equipment, which of the following should be the most readily accessible item in the back of an ambulance?\n\nA. Emergency childbirth kit\nB. Long bone splinting device\nC. Bleeding control supplies\nD. Stethoscope and penlight\nSee Phases of an Ambulance Call",
			"back": "Bleeding control supplies"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": "Characteristics of a safe ambulance operator include:\n\nA. a positive attitude about the ability to tolerate other drivers.\nB. realizing that lights and siren will be effective traffic tools.\nC. the ability to operate an ambulance at a high rate of speed.\nD. an offensive attitude about driving during an emergency call.\nSee Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques",
			"back": "a positive attitude about the ability to tolerate other drivers."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": "When arriving at the scene of an overturned tractor-trailer rig, you note that a green cloud is being emitted from the crashed vehicle. The driver is still in the truck; he is conscious but bleeding profusely from the head. After notifying the hazardous materials team, you should:\n\nA. park downhill from the scene.\nB. ask the driver to exit the vehicle.\nC. position the ambulance upwind.\nD. quickly gain access to the patient.\nSee Phases of an Ambulance Call",
			"back": "position the ambulance upwind."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": "Typically, medevac helicopters fly at speeds between:\n\nA. 120 and 140 mph.\nB. 100 and 120 mph.\nC. 150 and 200 mph.\nD. 130 and 150 mph.\nSee Air Medical Operations",
			"back": "130 and 150 mph."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": "Which of the following statements regarding the use of the warning lights and siren on the ambulance is correct?\n\nA. If the patient is stable, you may use the warning lights without the siren.\nB. If it is necessary to use the siren, you should tell the patient beforehand.\nC. Warning lights and siren should be avoided, even if the patient is unstable.\nD. It is generally acceptable to increase your speed if lights and siren are in use.\nSee Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques",
			"back": "If it is necessary to use the siren, you should tell the patient beforehand."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": "While en route to a call for a patient in cardiac arrest, you approach a stopped school bus with its red warning lights flashing. You should:\n\nA. pass the bus only after all the children have exited.\nB. slowly and carefully pass the bus on the left side.\nC. stop and wait until the warning lights stop flashing.\nD. back up and take an alternate route to the scene.\nSee Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques",
			"back": "stop and wait until the warning lights stop flashing."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": "During the transport phase of an ambulance call, it is most important to:\n\nA. complete the run form before arrival at the hospital.\nB. converse with the patient and provide reassurance.\nC. reassess the patient only if he or she deteriorates.\nD. reassess unstable patients at least every 15 minutes.\nSee Phases of an Ambulance Call",
			"back": "converse with the patient and provide reassurance."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": "The purpose of a jump kit is to:\n\nA. contain anything that you might need during the first 5 minutes of patient care.\nB. facilitate defibrillation within 5 to 10 minutes after making patient contact.\nC. carry advanced life support equipment approved by the EMS medical director.\nD. manage a critically injured patient until he or she is loaded into the ambulance.\nSee Phases of an Ambulance Call",
			"back": "contain anything that you might need during the first 5 minutes of patient care."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": "Portable and mounted suction units must be powerful enough to generate a vacuum of at least ____ mm Hg when the tubing is clamped.\n\nA. 400\nB. 100\nC. 200\nD. 300\nSee Phases of an Ambulance Call",
			"back": "300"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": "Common safety equipment carried on the ambulance includes all of the following, except:\n\nA. turnout gear.\nB. safety goggles.\nC. face shields.\nD. hazardous materials gear.\nSee Phases of an Ambulance Call",
			"back": "hazardous materials gear."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": "Hydroplaning of the ambulance on wet roads would most likely occur at speeds of greater than _____ mph.\n\nA. 30\nB. 20\nC. 10\nD. 15\nSee Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques",
			"back": "30"
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-38",
		"label": "Chapter 38"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}